### **Edgars Grazulis**

London, UK Phone: +44 07914500965

Email: grazulisedgars@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/grazulisedgars95/

Portfolio: https://github.com/grazulisedgars

### **Profile**

Solid understanding of web development, possessing HTML, CSS and JavaScript coding knowledge. My experience in website building extends beyond platforms like Squarespace, Wix, and WordPress to include proficiency in Git version control and GitHub. This expertise allows me to collaborate effectively with development teams and contribute to projects involving code management, making me a valuable asset in web development and collaboration efforts.

#### **Technical Skills**

- Web development with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript
- Code versioning using Git and GitHub
- Node.js and React
- RESTful-compliant network requests
- Deploy web-based applications using Netlify

- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals Certificate
- Great knowledge of Adobe platforms: Premiere Pro, Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign
- Excellent knowledge of MS
   Office Package

I

### **Projects**

#### EG-Team-GEN | https://github.com/grazulisedgars/EG-Team-GEN |

- Summary: This Node.js command-line application generates a team profile HTML page by collecting information about team members
- Role: Sole author
- Tools: Node.js, Inquirer, Jest, JavaScript, CSS

# Go\_Where | <a href="https://github.com/grazulisedgars/Go\_Where">https://grazulisedgars.github.io/Go\_Where/</a>

 Summary: App should help you decide your next holiday destination either sunny or snowy

- Role: Set up collaborative Git project/ Get API keys for OpenWeather + functionality/
   Event Listeners to toggle between start and second screen
- Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, DailyMotion API, OpenWeather API, Bootstrap

### **Work Experience**

## Small Green Shoots | Project Assistant | London, UK 03/2018 - 04/2023

At Small Green Shoots I am responsible for the smooth running of our arts fundraising program (Arts Council, Help Musicians and PRS) which provides funding for several music and community start-ups in London, SE and the Midlands. This includes producing microsites (SquareSpace, Wordpress applications), budgets, marketing plans and evaluation presentations. Here I work in a team to tight deadlines, researching best prices and local suppliers and developing and maintaining ongoing relationships with clients.

## Various Artist Management | Management Assistant | London, UK 01/2019 - 05/2019

I researched venues, session musicians and European touring locations for a variety of artists including The Libertines, Spiritualized, The Hunna and Tom Grennan. I also created "one sheet" presentations for individual artists which were then serviced to international programmers and media outlets. Additionally, developing budgets for European artist tours, which is giving me a real insight into booth technical and artist related costs and time planning.

#### **Education**

## Front-End Web Development | Edx Skills for Life Bootcamp | Certificate 09/2023 - 01/2024

Throughout the course, I gained proficiency in numerous marketable technologies including HTML, CSS and JavaScript, Node.js and React, Github and Git version control. Bootcamp taught me how to create visually compelling layouts with a focus on UX design principles.

BMus Music Performance with Music Management | University of West London | Bachelors degree GRADE 2:1 09/2015 - 05/2018

London College of Music, University of West London. Developing musicianship skills as well as analytical and critical abilities, enriched with business, management and marketing skills.